Guide to the Manny Harriman Video Oral History Collection ALBA.VIDEO.048
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: Manny Harriman Oral History Project
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview; VALB Dinner Fundraiser for Nicaragua Ambulances, Apr 14, 1985 (Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-059)
    Tape contains two events. Recording of VALB Fundraiser for Nicaragua ambulances (4/14/1985); and fifth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff discussing German and Austrian guerillas (4/17/1985).
  - Gold, Irving Interview, Jan 26, 1987 (Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-060)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Gold.
  - Shuldiner, Anne (Anna Goldman) Interview, Feb 4, 1987 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-061)
    First of two tapes containing interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Anna Goldman, who served under the name Anne Shuldiner.
  - Shuldiner, Anne (Anna Goldman) Interview, Feb 4, 1987 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-062)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Anna Goldman, who served under the name Anne Shuldiner.
  - Goldring, Benjamin (Ben) Interview, Aug 12, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-063)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Goldring.
  - Goldstein, [Abraham] David Interview, Sep 21, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-064)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran David Goldstein.
  - Goldstein, Benjamin (Butch) Memorial, Sep 29, 1985 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-065)
    Recording of memorial service for Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Butch Goldstein.
  - Goldstein, Maynard Interview, Dec 18, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-066)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Maynard Goldstein.
  - Goloff, Harry Interview, Nov 2, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-067)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Goloff.
  - Gonshak, Samuel Interview, Dec 19, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-068)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Samuel Gonshak.
  - Gottlieb, Albert (Al) Interview, Jul 28, 1985 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-069)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Gottlieb.
  - Graeber, Kenneth (Ken) Interview, May 1, 1985 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-070)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ken Graeber.
  - Grell, Fritz discussed by LaVerne Grell; Perley Payne, Jr. Interview, undated (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-071)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with LaVerne Grell, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fritz Grell; and interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Perley Payne, Jr.
  - Grumet, Leonard discussed by Donna Bemiss, Jul 28, 1985 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-072)
    Interview with Donna Bemiss, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leonard Grumet, who died July 9, 1959.
  - Haggerty, George discussed by Alice Haggerty, Jul 11, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-073)
    Interview with Alice Haggerty, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran George Haggerty.
  - Hakam, Harry Interview, Jul 12, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-074)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Hakam.
  - Hakam, Harry Interview, Aug 15, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-075)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Hakam.
  - Harris, Sidney (Sid) discussed by Paul Harris and Manny Harriman, undated (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-076)
    Discussion between Manny Harriman and Paul Harris, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Harris, about son's view of his father.
  - Hautaniemi, Joseph Interview, Sep 3, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-077)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Joseph (Joe) Hautaniemi.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-078)
    First of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-079)
    Second of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-080)
    Third of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heisler, Gus Interview, Aug 14, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-081)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Heisler.
  - Heisler, Gus Interview, Aug 14, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-082)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Heisler.
  - Hill Liebert, Josephine Interview, Jun 11, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-083)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade x-ray technician Josephine Hill, who may have served under the name Josephine Liebert.
  - Hinman, Loyal (Luke) Interview, Sep 7, 1985 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-084)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Luke Hinman.
  - Holborn, Harry Interview, Jun 27, 1985 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-085)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Holborn.
  - Hollander, Herman (Hy) Interview, Feb 12, 1987 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-086)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Hy Hollander.
  - Holtzman, Benjamin (Ben) Interview, Sep 13, 1986 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-087)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Holtzman.
  - Hovan, John Interview, Sep 4, 1986 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-088)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran John Hovan.
  - Junas, Stanely (Stan) Interview, May 3, 1986 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-089)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stan Junas.
  - Katzman, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Apr 9, 1986 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-090)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Katzman.
  - Poling, Eugene Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-091)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Eugene Poling, and third of three tapes containing interview with Sid Kaufman.
  - Kaye, George Interview, Aug 23, 1985 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-092)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran George Kaye.
  - Keenan, Thomas Interview, Jan 25, 1987 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-093)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Thomas Keenan.
  - Keir Jr., Duncan Interview; Clifton Amsbury Interview; Samuel Mendelowitz (Curley Mende) Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-094)
    Tape contains three interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Duncan Keir, Jr.; interview with veteran Clifron Amsbury; and interview with Samuel (Sam) Mendelowitz, who was also known as Curley Mende.
  - Keller, Fred Interview, Apr 2, 2985 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-095)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fred Keller.
  - Keller, Fred Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-096)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fred Keller; and first of three tapes containing interview with veteran Sid Kaufman.
  - Simon, John discussed by Ruth Simon; Hyman (Hy) and Ruth Rosner Interview; and Armand Keossian (Arnold Kerin) Interview, undated (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-097)
    Tape contains three interviews[?]. Interview with Ruth Simon, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran "Doc" John Simon; interview with veteran Hy Rosner and his wife, Ruth Rosner; and first of two interviews with veteran Armand Keossian (Arnold Kerin).
  - Keossian, Armand (Arnold Kerin) Interview; Rudolph (Rudy) Corbin Interview, undated (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-098)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Armand Kerin[?]; and first of two tapes containing interview with veteran Rudy Corbin.
  - Koslow, Al Interview, Nov 28, 1986 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-099)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Koslow.
  - Kramer, Jacob (Jack) Interview, Feb 28, 1986 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-100)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Kramer.
  - Kutnik, Lee Interview, Jul 16, 1985 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-101)
    Interview with San Francisco Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade organizer[?] Lee Kutnik.
  - Landis, Arthur Interview, Jan 14, 1985 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-102)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Arthur Landis.
  - Landis, Arthur Interview; Irving (Irv) Goff Interview, Jan 16, 1985 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-103)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Arthur Landis; and sixth of six tapes containing interview wi veteran Irv Goff. [Goff interview may be duplicate of an interview on V 48-055-59.]
  - Levine, Benjamin (Lane) Interview, May 3, 1986 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-104)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Benjamin Levine, also known as Ben Lane.
  - Lee, Harold Interview, Apr 7, 1986 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-105)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harold Lee.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-106)
    First of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-107)
    Second of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987 (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-108)
    Third of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-109)
    Fourth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-110)
    Fifth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Levine, Sidney (Sid) Interview, Jul 25, 1985 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-111)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Levine.
  - Levine, Sidney (Sid) Interview, Jul 26, 1985 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-112)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Levine.
  - Lloyd, Thomas (Tom) Interview, Sep 8, 1986 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-113)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Tom Lloyd.
  - Love, Vaughn Interview, Aug 27, 1986 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-114)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Vaughn Love. Includes a viewing copy.
  - Love, Vaughn Interview, Aug 28, 1986 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-115)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Vaughn Love.
  - Lucid, John (Jack) discussed by Kirsten and Robert Lucid, undated (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-116)
    Interview with Kirsten Lucid, wife of, and Robert Lucid, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Lucid.
  - Malbin, Virginia Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-117)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran (or nurse) Virginia Malbin; and second of three tapes containing interview with veteran Sid Kaufman.
  - Harris Marantz, Ray Interview, undated (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-118)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Ray Marantz, who served under the name Ray Harris.
  - McCarthy, Bill Interview, Aug 25, 1985 (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-119)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Bill McCarthy.
  - MacLeod, Donald (Don) Interview; Fritz Grell discussed by LaVerne Grell, undated (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-120)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Don MacLeod; and first of two tapes containing interview with LaVerne Grell, son of veteran Fritz Grell.
  - McDaniels, Eluard Luchell Interview, Aug 26, 1985 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-121)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Eluard Luchell McDaniels. User copy available
  - Madigan, Frank Memorium, May 1, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-122)
    Recording of memorial service for Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Frank Madigan.
  - Merriman, Marian Wachtel Interview, Sep 9, 1985 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-123)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Marian Wachtel Merriman.
  - Merriman, Robert (Bob) discussed by Marian Wachtel Merriman, Sep 9, 1985 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-124)
    Interview with Marian Wachtel Merriman about Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Bob Merriman.
  - Minor, Ben Interview, Sep 8, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-125)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Minor.
  - Mitchell, Irving Interview, Mar 6, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-126)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Mitchell.
  - Nelson, Steve Interview, Aug 30, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-127)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Steve Nelson. User copy available
  - Nelson, Steve Interview, Aug 30, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-128)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Steve Nelson. User copy available
  - Nitzberg, Leo discussed by Judy Nitzberg, Jul 9, 1985 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-129)
    Interview with Judy Nitzberg, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leo Nitzberg. May also contain interview of his son.
  - Nitzberg, Leo discussed by Mariam Johnson, May 3, 1986 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-130)
    Interview with Mariam Johnson, friend of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leo Nitzberg, who died in 1981. Mariam Johnson reads the eulogy she delivered at his memorial service.
  - Norton, Thomas (Tom) Interview, Jul 18, 1985 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-131)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Tom Norton.
  - Nusser, Charles Interview, undated (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-132)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Charles Nusser.
  - Olsen, Leonard Interview, Jul 12, 1985 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-133)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leonard Olsen.
  - O'Malley, Thomas Interview, Aug 31, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-134)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Thomas O'Malley.
  - Parker, Max discussed by Mary Parker, Aug 25, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-135)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Mary Parker, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Parker.
  - Parker, Max discussed by Mary Parker, Aug 25, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-136)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Mary Parker, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Parker.
  - Payne, Earle Interview, May 2, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-137)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Earle Payne.
  - Peck, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Feb 6, 1987 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-138)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Peck.
  - Perlman, Norman (Norm) Interview, Feb 22, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-139)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Norm Perlman.
  - Perrone, John Interview, 1986-1987? (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-139a)
  - Persilly, Coleman Interview, undated (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-140)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Coleman Persilly.
  - Pike, William W. Interview, Aug 13, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-141)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau physician Dr. William W. Pike.
  - Postek, Stanley Interview, Jun 27, 1985 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-142)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Postek.
  - Prago, Albert Interview, Aug 14, 1986 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-143)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Prago.
  - Rappaport, Irving William Interview, Jan 27, 1987 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-144)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Rappaport.
  - Reed, Robert L. Interview, Sep 4, 1985 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-145)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Robert Reed.
  - Rigamonte, Gino Interview, Aug 5, 1985 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-146)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gino Rigamonte.
  - Bell, Hilda (Roberts) Interview, May 4, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-149)
    Interivew with American Medical Bureau nurse Hilda Bell Roberts, who served under the name Hilda Bell.
  - Robbins, Albert (Al) Interview, Dec 17, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-147)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Robbins.
  - Robbins, Albert (Al) Interview, Jan 4, 1987 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-148)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Robbins.
  - Rollins, Wade Interview, Aug 25, 1985 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-150)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Wade Rollins.
  - Romer, Edna Interview, Mar 12, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-151)
    Interivew with American Medical Bureau nurse Edna Romer.
  - Romer, Samuel (Sam) discussed by Edna Romer, Mar 12, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-152)
    Interview with Edna Romer, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Romer.
  - Klein, Herman (Gabby) Interview, Apr 4, 1985 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-153)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Herman (Gabby) Klein.
  - Klein, Herman (Gabby) Rosenstein Interview, Mar 3, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-154)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Herman Rosenstein, who served under the name Herman (Gabby) Klein.
  - Ross, Adolph Interview, Aug 23, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-155)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Adolph Ross.
  - Schiff, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Dec 4, 1986 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-156)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Schiff.
  - Schlekau, Walter Interview, Jul 6, 1985 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-157)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Walter Schlekau.
  - Schneider, Theodore (Ted) Interview, Dec 22, 1986 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-158)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ted Schneider.
  - Schwerner, Moses (Murray) Interview, Apr 12, 1985 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-159)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Murray Schwerner, who served under the name Moses Schwerner.
  - Secundy, Louis Interview, Dec 17, 1986 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-160)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Louis Secundy.
  - Sennett, William Interview; Frank Brown Interview, Jun 24, 1985 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-161)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran William Sennett; and interview with veteran Frank Brown. Use Copy available
  - Shafran, Jack Interview, Nov 15, 1986 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-162)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Shafran.
  - Shafran, Jack Interview, undated (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-163)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Shafran.
  - Shaker, Kenneth (Ken) Interview, undated (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-164)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ken Shaker.
  - Shosteck, Sidney discussed by Lawrence Darow Gurewitz, undated (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-165)
    Interview with Lawrence Darow Gurewitz, cousin of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sidney Shosteck.
  - Shufer, Max Interview, Sep 28, 1986 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-166)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Shufer.
  - Simon, John Leopold Interview, Nov 16, 1986 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-167)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran John Simon.
  - Rackley, Mildred (Simon) Interview; Maurice Friedman discussed by Muriel Eldridge, undated (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-168)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Mildred Rackley Simon, who served under the name Mildred Rackley; and interview with Muriel Eldridge, sister of veteran Maurice Friedman.
  - Smith, Randall B. (Pete) Interview, Jul 30, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-169)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Randall B. (Pete) Smith.
  - Smorodin, Abe Interview, Dec 23, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-170)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Abe Smorodin.
  - Soloway, Irving ("Doc" Fred) discussed by Ruth Pinkston, undated (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-171)
    Interview with Ruth Pinkston, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran "Doc" Fred Soloway, aka Irving Soloway.
  - Wachsman, Rose Sorkin Interview, Jan 23, 1987 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-172)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Rose Wachsman Sorkin, who served under the name Rose Wachsman.
  - Sperber, Gus (Gustav) Interview, Feb 5, 1987 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-173)
    First with two tapes containing interview of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Sperber.
  - Sperber, Gus (Gustav) Interview, Feb 5, 1987 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-174)
    Second with two tapes containing interview of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Sperber.
  - Spiller, Samuel Interview, Nov 6, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-175)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Samuel Spiller.
  - Staats, Frank discussed by Leonard Olsen, Jul 11, 1985 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-176)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leonard Olsen, discussing veteran Frank Staats.
  - Steck, Robert Interview, Sep 27, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-177)
    First of two interviews with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Robert Steck.
  - Steck, Robert Interview, Sep 27, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-178)
    Second of two interviews with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Robert Steck.
  - Steffens, Robert discussed by Nita[?] Steffens, Jul 29, 1985 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-179)
    Interview with Nita[?] Steffens, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Robert Steffens.
  - Susman, William (Bill) Interview, Sep 10, 1986 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-180)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran William (Bill) Susman. User copy available
  - Susman, William Interview, Sep 10, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-181)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran William Susman.
  - Tabb, Herbert Interview, Dec 9, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-182)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Herbert Tabb.
  - Thayer, Donald (Don) discussed by Mildred Thayer, Jul 20, 1985 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-183)
    Interview with Mildred Thayer, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Don Thayer.
  - Thompson, David (Dave) Interview, Jul 7, 1985 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-184)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Dave Thompson. User copy available
  - Thorton, Mark Binnes discussed by Nathan James (Nate) Thorton, Jul 24, 1985 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-185)
    Interview with Nathan James (Nate) Thorton, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Mark Thorton.
  - Thorton, Nathan James (Nate) Interview, Jul 24, 1985 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-186)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Nate Thorton.
  - Timpson, Arthur Edward discussed by Anne Bartak[?] Timpson, Mar 12, 1987 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-187)
    Interview with Anne Bartak[?] Timpson, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Arthur Edward Timpson.
  - Tishup, Victor Interview, Sep 29, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-188)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Victor Tishup.
  - Toney, Anthony Interview, Sep 24, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-189)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Anthony Toney.
  - Torrance, Mary P. Interview, Apr 10, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-190)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse[?] Mary P. Torrance.
  - Toutoloff, John Interview, Dec 6, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-191)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran John Toutoloff.
  - Toutoloff, John Interview, Dec 6, 1986 (Box 16, Item ALBA V 48-192)